Well, apparently I've discovered that
I can take these yawn-filled days
And turn them into movies
I've found the secret and trick to it
Under this sky where we don't get along
I closed my heart and locked it
That's how I've managed to live my life
And the melodies now overlap
I wanted a sign, no matter how small
That I could actually find
better than any streetlight
I put a ribbon on each of the
sights that my eyes pick out
And I collect them like souvenirs
as I continue down this path home
The seasons each say hello,
and I shed a few tears as I go
Where should I begin to talk about
this way home that you've given me?
I walk and walk and sometimes
rush on my way to see you
I run and run, wait, no, I should
still walk on my way to see you
Oh, you don't say! Really?
Yes, really! That's why I've been saying...
Oh? Good morning, Mrs. Forger.
What's the matter? You look so blue.
Am I going to be tossed aside?
Huh?
When I really think about it, it never
mattered if I won that tennis match.
What in the world?
Her husband cheated on her. I just know it.
Oh, heavens! What an awful man!
Well, look at how handsome he is!
I guess it's to be expected.
Women just flock to him
like fruit flies on fruit.
I hope the missus doesn't sell
him off to the Secret Police
like the woman in apartment 15
did with her husband.
Is Yor concerned about Nightfall?
Not good.
This would be bad for my cover,
and if she just happened to
mention it to her brother...
So that's what happened.
That utter bastard!
I'll execute him immediately!
I'll get the entire
State Security Service on it!
I can definitely see that happening.
THE ROLE OF A MOTHER AND WIFE
Wah!
Borf...
Scruffy, scruffy, scruff!
I've got you cornered now, Bondman!
Curse you, King Scruff!
Scruffy, scruffy, scruffy, scruff!
Anya's gonna draw now.
Heh. I'll allow you to use the magical
color-changing pen that I invented.
Oh, yeah! I even brought a
Frisbee for the goodest boy!
Borf!
Hooray!
So, yeah. Thanks for looking after the pla—
Urk!
No, seriously! How many times do I have
to tell you I ain't no babysitter?!
I already explained this to you.
If I don't clear up Yor's misunderstanding
involving my coworker,
it'll affect the mission.
Well, have your damn family meeting at home!
It'd be hard to talk to her about
these things in front of the child.
Anyway, here.
Don't try to solve everything
with money, you damn villain!
Anyway, time to go to
the park, kids! Let's enjoy!
Yay!
Borf.
Yor.
I'm sorry. I'm late because
I had to work overtime.
Well, you can relax now.
So what are we...
I thought we could go out
and enjoy some drinks.
I know a great place.
Here's your Red Queen.
Thank you.
I'll have my usual scotch.
Thank you for always doing the
chores and taking care of Anya.
Cheers.
Oh, ch-ch-cheers...
I-I wonder what's going on.
He seems like he wants
to talk about something.
Thanks for everything you've done.
I'll enjoy life with my new wife now.
Good evening.
Tee-hee.
Oh, I knew it!
By the way, Yor...
About Fiona the other day—
Wai—whoa!
Yor?
S-Sorry about that...
What should I do? This is a problem.
If he ends this relationship...
Well... This was always a
marriage of convenience.
I have no right to say anything
about Loid's personal life.
Um...
If Loid has romantic feelings for her,
that means I'm no longer of use,
and I should just leave.
Um, Loid...
If this is what you want,
I'd be happy to, um...
Uh...
Huh? But why?
Um...
My throat keeps closing up,
and the words won't come out.
Is it because I want this life to continue?
But you mustn't, Yor!
Loid's happiness is more important
than protecting yourself.
You need to tell him that!
Oh, alcohol!
Give me strength! Open, throat!
That's not enough! Let me have yours, Loid!
Yor! You're going to die
if you drink like that!
Woid...
Huh?
Jush who ish dat woman?!
Are you in wuv wif her, Woid?!
I was just about to explain all that...
Oh, I shee! Sho you were in a werationship!
I jush wanted to giff you my bwessings!
What am I even shaying?!
Please calm down, Yor...
She's just a colleague of mine.
I promise you, our relationship
is nothing more than that.
Being such a hot guy must be rough.
Ish fine. I know I'm a fwailure.
I'm nowhere near ash pwetty ash Hiona.
Have you... heard a word I've said?
Hm? Wait...
But you shaid before dat
I wash pwetty, too.
Wash dat jush a wie?!
I thought she was fearing the end of our
contract because she lost faith in her abilities.
Is this actually jealousy?
Are you awready shick of me?
Wait, does Yor have romantic feelings for me?!
I am Twilight.
I have had relationships with countless
women for the sake of my missions.
I'm sorry I've made you worry, Yor.
If Yor truly feels this way about me,
I simply must take advantage of this.
Which means... time for
Operation Honey Trap.
But I want you to have faith in me.
Huh?!
Do you hate me now?
Huh? U-Um, no... I wouldn't shay that...
Yor, after spending so much time by your side,
I've finally realized my true feelings.
Um... W-W-W-Woi...
W-W-W-Wo...
Woi?!
Yor, let's get married for rea—
Huh? Wha' did I jush do?!
Oooh...
I was so wrong!
The force behind that kick...
That wasn't from embarrassment.
That was true rejection!
There weren't even a hint of
romantic feelings there!
I got cocky! I'm so sorry!
Are you awwight, Woid?!
I don't understand! What was
that mood of hers just now?!
Did she initiate some high-level reverse
trap to get me to initiate my honey trap?
Is Yor a spy? No, calm down,
Twilight. That can't be it.
I'm sho sowwy! I'm sho sowwy! Woid! Woi...
I can't let my guard down like that.
Somehow, being with Yor throws me off...
Beneath their silver shine, drift to sleep...
A song?
How nostalgic. That's a lullaby
I used to hear all the time.
O sweet prince of mine...
Drift to sleep...
Mother?
I don't know the rest of the words...
Good mworning, Woid...
Wh-Where am I?!
How long was I out?!
We're at a nearby park.
The barthender shaid we were
being too woud and kicked ush out.
You were only asweep for about five minutes.
I haven't been knocked out like that
since my instructor got rough with me!
You've let your guard
down way too much, Loid!
Also, why I was I using
her lap as a pillow?!
I'm very sowwy, Woid.
Of course you'd get shick of
a musclehead woman wike me...
When I was little...
Though I can't remember her face anymore,
I loved being in my mother's arms.
Even on nights when we could've
been bombed at any moment,
just having my mother by my side
allowed me to sleep soundly.
My mother was strong.
Anya tells me all the time that
even if she's in danger, her Mama
will come save her, so she'll be okay.
The reason she's able to
smile and have fun like that
is because you're a safe place for her, Yor.
We agents of the state have been
trying to rebuild this world
through our blood, sweat, and tears.
Yet she managed to accomplish
that all on her own.
You're very strong, Yor.
This may be rude to say
to an unmarried woman,
but you're already a wonderful mother.
I don't think mine is the kind of
strength you're talking about...
I have absolutely no intention of replacing
you in the role of her mother.
B-But Hiona...
Even if I had ever asked her to
take on the role of Anya's mother,
she has absolutely no parenting skills.
But in my cashe... I'd jush been
taking care of Yuri for sho long...
that I jusht twied to do
shomething similar.
But that's just it, though.
This is a skill you've been building
up ever since you were little,
which makes you unparalleled.
Have more confidence in yourself.
I would love for you to
continue being Anya's mother.
And to continue in the role of my wife.
I humbwy accept...
If you'll continue to have me.
Yor, your nose is running.
Pwease excuse me...
Should we head home?
Yesh, we should.
I'll make you shome hot
tea once we get home.
Mama and Papa are late.
They must be shacking up somewhere.
Where exactly do you learn to talk like that?
Mostly from Becky.
I hope they'll be home soon.
Hey, do you like your mom and dad?
I love them!
I see.
We're home.
Borf!
Mama and Papa are flirt...
...ing.
The hell, man?!
Did you try to put some moves
on her and get punched?!
No, no! Ish all my fault!
He's a chin monster.
Here, have a closer look!
Wait! Don't touch it!
Don't touch!
I'm actually surprised myself.
Back then, I never became attached to
anyone or anything other than my brother.
And yet...
I really can't let this place go.
The next day...
Loid! What in the world
happened to your chin?!
Wait, what?! You forgot everything
that happened yesterday?!
They had the same conversation
all over again.
So the social gathering is
finally happening next week.
Well...
They don't really apply to us just yet.
I'm gonna get eight Stella in no time.
Of course!
The mission so that Papa can be
friends with Second's Son's papa:
Operation Skoricks.
To make it a success, I must
become an Imperel Scooter
and go to the social event.
But...
Anya has sort of given up
on getting eight stars.
Whether it's studying...
or sports, I'm not getting better at all,
and my heart can't take more disappointment.
And that's why Anya is
giving her all to Plan B,
the Friendship Scheme,
to get closer to Second Son,
but that's not going well, either.
The heck are you looking at, huh?
Stupid daughter of that
violent, bribing doctor!
Anya is losing patience.
Oh, my heart is getting impatient
watching you like this, Anya!
I totally get it, Anya! It's so hard
to tell someone you love them!
Love?
I love Papa.
I love Mama.
I love peanuts.
I love cartoons.
Second Son...
Nope, nuh-uh.
Oh, look at you being all shy!
Be true to your heart!
Okay, I know! I'll help you
so he ends up liking you.
Boys always fall for how a girl looks.
If you get dressed up all cute and fancy,
he'll be head over heels for you in no time!
Oho.
Which means, next weekend...
We're going shopping together!
SHOPPING WITH FRIENDS
Anya's never been in a fancy car!
So exciting!
It's not bad, right?
And hey! I went all the way to your house,
and my precious Loid wasn't there! Why?!
Loid, oh Loid! Wherefore art thou, Loid?
Thank you for looking
after our daughter today.
Papa had an emergency at work.
Also, my precious Loid's
wife is way prettier in person.
She's definitely a worthy rival.
You mustn't commit adultery, my lady.
By the way, that pochette is
really cute. What's in it?
Um...
Lots of cold, hard cash.
Being on good terms with the Blackbells
will be extremely advantageous.
I'm sure intel will be willing
to splurge on the budget.
Take this.
That much?!
My allowance.
Oh, my precious Loid is so kind!
It's not that much, though.
Kids these days...
How many peanuts can I buy with this?
We're not buying peanuts.
We're buying clothes, my dear. Clothes.
Welcome, Miss Becky.
We've prepared quite a few pieces
from the Berlint Collection.
Thank you!
Are your family evil masterminds after all?
How much cold, hard cash do you have?
I've never even walked
around with cash before.
Usually, the shops come to me, but today,
I wanted to enjoy shopping with you,
so I rented out this whole department store.
Let's have you try on all kinds of outfits
and find the one that'll make him fall for you.
Lip-Reading Techniques
to Let You Truly Be Yourself
Read Minds and Become
More Beautiful.
Anya's Fall Collection
Clothes That'll Get Your Classmates to Love You
A Special Feature on Westalis Import Brands
A Telepath Girl's Styling Tutorial
Styling Tutorial
Forget All About Your School Uniform
Yes! Perfect, Anya!
You look adorable! But I'm still cuter.
That's right, Anya. Break free from
your shell and become a new you.
Hmm... Maybe we broke the shell a bit too much.
But you need to be aggressive
when it comes to fashion!
Perfect, Anya! I don't even get
it anymore, but it's perfect!
Reach out your hand and
go beyond fashion itself!
Fashion is hard...
Yeah... We don't know what he's into,
so it's hard to narrow down the choices.
But I wear the same clothes
every day at school.
I don't have a chance to
show off another outfit.
Of course our uniforms
are the same every day.
But if our instructor allows it,
we can wear our own clothes at the
dorm party at the end of the term.
That'll be your opportunity!
Oh, wait! If parents and guardians
are going to attend this party...
My, what a beautiful young lady.
I'm Anya's father, Loid.
Oh, no! I shouldn't have wasted so
much time finding clothes for Anya!
Shock!
Hey, what kind of clothes
does my precious Loid like?
So cute!
Maybe I'll go for an orthodox cute look.
Miss Becky!
How lovely!
Or perhaps something a bit more stylish?
You look amazing!
How about this?
Maybe I'll just go for a
more sophisticated look.
So mature!
Maybe I'll try out his wife's look.
It's perfect!
So cute!
Hmm... I don't know what to do anymore, either.
You looked lovely in all of them.
Anyway, I'll go ahead and buy all of them.
Thank you very much.
Which one do you want, Anya?
Anya's tummy is already very
full from all the outfits.
Really? Then do you want
to go look at some shoes?
I guess I'm a little tired, too.
I almost shopped myself to death...
To death? Are you actually going to die?
My lady, you have purchased too many things.
Wait! Are you in there somewhere, Martha?!
By the way, you haven't
bought anything yet, Anya.
I dunno what I want.
Fashion is hard.
Did you... not enjoy shopping with me?
I had fun!
This is Anya's first time shopping
with a friend! So exciting!
Friend?
I-In that case, let's get right back into it!
Let's look for something you want, Anya!
Cartoon merch is what calls my name.
They don't have anything
like that at this shop.
I think there's a plushie shop over there.
Who is Mister Sheep here?
Huh?
Oh, it's this department store's mascot.
Look over there.
Apparently, it's because they
started off selling wool.
So cute... I want this!
What? A key chain?
You're such a child, Anya.
It's to remember going shopping with you.
Huh?
To celebrate that we both overcame death.
Th-Then I'll also—
Listen well, Becky.
As the daughter of a top conglomerate,
you must only wear the finest things.
Here! I bought one for you, too.
Huh? When did you...
Anya is very good at doing big sister things.
But...
If you were to ignore
your friend's generosity,
you would be tarnishing the Blackbell name.
I'm sure that's exactly
what your father would say.
Th-Then I guess I don't have a choice.
It's a bit embarrassing,
but I guess I'll take it.
Thank you.
Becky should also be more honest.
Wait, why did we go shopping today, anyway?
I forget.
Well, whatever. Let's go home.
Becky's always so mean!
She always says mean things and bullies us!
What? What's wrong with calling you little
brats when that's exactly what you are?
That's quite enough, young lady!
Eden College? No!
Because I learned in nursery school
that no good comes from associating
with commoners.
This sucks.
Whatever. I guess smiling and going along with
those around you is the adult strategy here.
My lady, you mustn't think you know all
there is to know about everything and everyone.
Once you can stop doing that, you'll be
on your way to becoming a proper adult.
Listen to this, Martha!
There's this really interesting
girl in my class!
Maybe school's not so bad after all!
I'll get you something later...
I'm very happy for you, my lady.
Just this was 300 dalc?!
* Roughly 100,000 yen
It's the treasure Becky and me share.
Jealou...
Good morning!
Anya!
Morning, pwease.
We match!
We do!
I hope the teachers don't yell at us.
It's no problem!
You're right.
What's the matter, Lord Damian?
Nothing! Jeez!
FIRST CONTACT